yes.
はい
I just finished shooting one.
1個撮影終わったんですけど
yes.
はい
How was it?
どうでした?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
気 持 ち よ かった
I spoke to the first person earlier,
さっきも最初の方にお話させていただいて、
There are some circumstances, so
ちょっと 事情があるということで、
I think they came to this location this time to take pictures.
今回この場所にね、撮影に来てくれてると思うんですけど、
In the end, I came up with a proposal, and we got to know each other a little bit.
結局僕が提案があって、 ちょっと知り合い、
I called you Otomachi, just for me.
オトマチ呼んだんですよ、僕ちょっと
Talk about that person with your mouth.
その人のことを、 お口で
Wasn't it just a little below?
さっきちょっと、下じゃないですか
Down below.
下の方にね
I think I gave it out, but this time with my mouth,
出したと思うんですけど、 今回お口で、
I want you to do it.
やってほしいな
I want my friend to feel good about it.
僕の友達の気持ちよく差し上げてほしいな
I'd like a little help, or rather,
ちょっとお助けというか、 よりね、
That's what it feels like, what do you think?
っていう感じなんですけど、 どうですか?
I think it's a bad thing because I think you're in trouble.
お困りだと思うんで、 悪い話じゃないかなと思うんですけど、
I was just wondering what kind of person you called me once.
ちょっと一回どういう感じの人呼んだかって、
Would you like me to come in for a moment?
一 回ちょっと入ってきてもらうか
A little bit on this side.
ちょっとこっちの方に
Look, look, look!
見て見て、下ほら、もう
Too cute.
可愛すぎて
Is it okay?
いいんですか?
Are you touching your breasts?
おっぱい触ってますか?
Hey, my eyes.
ちょっと、目が
What do you think?
どうですか?
This person is a bit verbal, but...
この人なんですけど、 ちょっとお口でという感じなんですけど、
Do you want to do it?
やりますか?
Why not?
やらないですか?
Let's do it.
やろう
May I?
いいですか?
yes.
はい
May I?
いいですか?
Well then, wait a minute, then...
じゃあ、ちょっと、 じゃあ、
If you look this cute, you're already there.
こんな 可愛く見たらもう、 すでに
I'm fine with my own timing, so please give me a moment.
自分のタイミングでいいんで、 ちょっとお願いします
What does this dick taste like?
このチンコはどんな味すか?
picture?
え?
What does it taste like?
どんな味?
difficult?
難しい?
As for the gold balls, because they have properties, they accumulate.
金玉の方もさ、 性質あるから、溜まってるから
difficult.
難 しい
Do it properly.
ちゃんとして
Let's go.
いくよ
show me.
見せて
What does it taste like?
どんな味す?
Hmm.
うーん
Don't you know?
わかんない?
A lot came out.
いっぱい出たね
Okay, leave it as is.
いいよ、そのまま
Look more.
もっと見て
It's so erotic.
エロいっすね
Peace, on one side.
ピースしてよ、片方で
Can't you?
できない?
I can't.
できない
Show me your hands.
見 せて、手に
This thing that just came out, that came out in your mouth,
これ、今出た、お口の中で出たやつは、
What kind of person is it?
なんていうやつですか?
What do you call it?
なんていうもん?
Seshi.
せし
Well, as promised, I'll be able to help you even more.
じゃあ、お約束通り、 よりお助けできるように、
Please excuse me.
失礼させていただきます
I haven't taken a shower yet.
さっきまだ、 シャワーまだ浴びてないもんね
Shall I go take a shower?
シャワー行こうか
Well then, here it is.
じゃあ、 いったんここで